
{
    "softQuestion":[
                   
                    {"question": "What do you look forward to most in the next six weeks?",
                    "id": "0",
                    "answer": [
                               
                               ],
                    "firstName":"John", "lastName":"Doe"},
                    {"question": "What do you look forward to most in the next six weeks?",
                    "id": "1",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "hmmm Roadtrip hopefully"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"John", "lastName":"Doe"},
                    {"question": "Do you prefer to call or text?",
                    "id": "2",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "call"} , {"answer": "Text"},{ "answer": "Both"}, {"answer": "Neither"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Anna", "lastName":"Smith"},
                    {"question": "Comedy, Drama, Science Fiction, Animation, Action, or Horror?",
                    "id": "3",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "COMEDY"} , {"answer": "Drama"},{ "answer": "Science Fiction"}, {"answer": "Action"},
                               {"answer": "Horror"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "Are your parents married/separated/divorced, or other?",
                    "id": "4",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "MARRIED"} , {"answer": "Separated"},{ "answer": "Divorced"}, {"answer": "Other"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "What color are your eyes?",
                    "id": "5",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "BROWN"} , {"answer": "Blue"},{ "answer": "Green"}, {"answer": "Other"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"John", "lastName":"Doe"},
                    {"question": "Do you own slippers?",
                    "id": "6",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Anna", "lastName":"Smith"},
                    {"question": "What are you wearing right now?",
                    "id": "7",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "What is your favorite Holiday?",
                    "id": "8",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "Where is your favorite place to be?",
                    "id": "9",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"John", "lastName":"Doe"},
                    {"question": "Where is your least favorite place to be?",
                    "id": "10",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Anna", "lastName":"Smith"},
                    {"question": "What did you fear was going to get you at night as a child?",
                    "id": "11",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "What color is your bedroom?",
                    "id": "12",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "How many pillows do you sleep with?",
                    "id": "13",
                    "answer": [
                    
                    ],

                    "firstName":"John", "lastName":"Doe"},
                    {"question": "What is your favorite season?",
                    "id": "14",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Anna", "lastName":"Smith"},
                    {"question": "How many states have you lived in?",
                    "id": "15",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "Do you like sushi?",
                    "id": "16",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "Do you like sushi?",
                    "id": "17",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "Do you like sushi?",
                    "id": "18",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "Do you like sushi?",
                    "id": "19",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"},
                    {"question": "Do you like sushi?",
                    "id": "20",
                    "answer": [
                               { "answer": "NO"} , {"answer": "NO"},{ "answer": "NO"}, {"answer": "NO"}
                               ],
                    "firstName":"Peter", "lastName":"Jones"}
                
                    
              ]
}

